两人桌
Table for two.
别担心  他刚大小便完
And don't worry, he just went.
三号桌的客人也刚在卡座大小便完
So did the guy at booth three.
麦克斯  那个警察带了缉毒犬
Max, that cop has a drug-sniffing dog.
很高兴认识你  再会
So, it was nice knowing you.
你说啥来着
What's that, now?
-你要搬走了吗  -麦克斯  快灭掉
- You're moving out? - Max, put that away!
闻起来像威利·纳尔逊头巾抽屉的臭味
It smells like Willie Nelson's bandana drawer in here.
麦克斯  你有看到那个欧丽斯欧各地吗
Max, have you seen the olicepay ogday?
这大麻劲儿太强
Uh, that pot was too strong.
我看到一只花栗鼠在跟我说话
There's a chipmunk talking to me.
我的天啊  那是一只缉毒犬
Heavens, that's a drug-sniffing dog!
厄尔余生都得在监狱里度过了
Earl will spend the rest of his life behind bars.
所以大概就是两周啦
So, like, two weeks?
厄尔  注意  一点钟方向有缉毒犬
Earl, heads up. Narc dog at 1:00.
也可能是6点钟方向
Or it might be 6:00.
但绝对是420[大麻]
But it's definitely 420.
所以她就准许带狗进来
So, she can bring that dog in here,
而我却不许带我的"精神支持用妓女"
but I can't bring my emotional support hooker.
我不忍直视厄尔被狗撕成碎片
I can't watch a dog tear Earl to pieces.
小家伙来  坐下
Hey there, fella. Sit.
把小爪爪给我
All right, now give me that paw.
我有个小礼物给你  吃吧
Now here's what I got for you. There you go.
我对狗就是有一套
I have a way with dogs.
应该说我的大麻饼干有一套
Well, my marijuana biscuits do.
所以我把它命名为"狗不叫饼干"
That's why I call them Hush Puppies.
阿憨  如果你不介意  我跟这狗
Hey, Han, if it's cool, me and the dog
要一起去看最新的《星球大战》电影
are gonna go see the new Star Wars movie.
麦克斯  你猜我跟鲍比明晚要做什么
Max, guess what Bobby and I are doing tomorrow night?
还记得我一直超想去哪里吗
Where have I been dying to go?
除不在墨西哥快餐店里的诊所外
Besides a doctor's office that's not in a Chipotle.
不好意思  必胜客医生还得排队的好吗
Sorry, Dr. Pizza Hut has a waiting list.
大家安安
Hey, everybody!
我有点担心芭芭拉脑子不好
Oh, I'm worried that Barbara's not smart.
她连我的电邮都不回
Yeah, she doesn't even return my e-mails.
我觉得她有奥列格的DNA
I think she has Oleg's DNA.
这里大多数的椅子也都有沾到
So do most of the chairs in here.
这就是为什么我每天从自己家里带椅子来
That's why I bring my chair from home every day.
虽然坐地铁时会遭到侧目
I mean, it's awkward on the subway,
但反正我也不想坐在地铁椅子上
but I don't wanna sit on those seats either.
苏菲  孩子笨别赖我  我家人都特聪明
Sophie, don't blame me. My family's very smart.
我们赢了乌克兰版的《家庭问答》节目
We won Family Feud in Ukraine,
要把对方家庭杀光可是很需要智慧的
and it takes intelligence to kill another family.
我们就别自己骗自己了
Who are we kidding?
你就是个空有皮囊的傻逼
You're a gorgeous moron.
但我们该怎么处置这个傻孩子啊
But what are we gonna do with a dumb baby?
或许我们该问问阿憨
Maybe we should ask Han.
他也是个傻孩子
He's a dumb baby.
不许说阿憨是傻孩子
Hey, don't call Han a dumb baby.
他可是凭自己的力量与智慧
He managed to pull that stupid vest
把自己的大猪头给套进那白痴背心呢
over his giant potato head all by himself.
不是凭自己  是我帮忙的
Nope. I had to help him.
开始觉得我为了拿包代糖跑出来
Starting to think the Splenda packet I came out for
真是得不偿失了
wasn't worth it.
-小美人你好吗  -你也好啊  小帅哥
- Hey, gorgeous. - Hello, yourself, beautiful.
鲍比  好消息
Bobby, great news...
你猜猜我们明晚要做什么
guess what we're doing tomorrow night?
明晚吗  我没空
Tomorrow night? I can't.
我有一个爱好没有告诉你
I have a hobby that I haven't told you about
因为我觉得你不会喜欢
because I don't think it's something you'll like.
你的爱好是不废话直接讲故事重点吗
Oh, so is your hobby getting to the point of a story quickly?
也绝对不是夸奖
It's definitely not acknowledging
我新的凯撒沙拉食谱很棒
my new Caesar salad recipe.
宝宝还在等呢
Still waiting.
宝宝还想吐呢
Still nauseous.
我敢打赌鲍比喜欢跟死尸做爱
Well, I bet you Bobby's into doing dead people.
他一脸就是那种人的长相
Yeah, he just has that look.
鲍比  我求你了  就告诉我吧
Bobby, for the love of God, just tell me.
无论你有什么爱好  也惨不过她说的那个啊
Whatever hobby you have, it can't be worse than that.
好吧  卡洛琳  我就大胆向你承认吧
Fine, Caroline, I'm just gonna come out and say it.
我喜欢打保龄球
I like to bowl.
你确定你要承认不是
And you're sure you don't wanna
你其实喜欢跟死尸做爱嘛
go with the dead people thing?
不过打保龄球也玩玩而已嘛  对吧
But bowling's just a hobby, right?
你也就偶尔...
Something you only do...
每周二晚上都打
Every Tuesday night.
我加了保龄球队  在球馆有个人置物柜
I'm on a team. I have a locker at the alley.
那个我跟你说是月亮的刺青
And that tattoo I told you was the moon,
其实是个保龄球
it's a bowling ball.
你为什么没跟我说这事
Why didn't you tell me?
因为我们很少在聊我的事
We don't talk about me a lot.
我觉得更重要的是
I thought it would be more important
在我难得有发言权时  先说我对坚果过敏
to tell you about my nut allergy when I had the floor.
你对坚果过敏吗
You have a nut allergy?
保龄球手吗  赞
Bowler? Nice!
我在少管所时也是保龄球队的
I was on a bowling team in juvie.
队名叫"狱卒把我们带到
We were called The Girls Who Escaped
保龄球馆后就逃跑的姑娘们"
when the Guards Took Us to the Bowling Alley.
这队名很难印到衣服上吧
That'd be hard to put on a shirt.
我们不穿衣服啊
Oh, we didn't wear shirts.
卡洛琳  我知道你不会喜欢保龄球
Caroline, I knew bowling wouldn't be your thing.
就像你读"欧棒棒"餐厅时  名字也乱读
You don't pronounce any of the Ns in Au Bon Pain.
那是因为正确法式发音是"欧胖胖"
That's because it's Au Bon Pain.
我们可以有不同的爱好啊
We can have separate things.
鲍比  其实呢  谈恋爱的一部分
Bobby, you know what? Part of being in a relationship
就是要学会接受新事物
is being open to trying new things.
而既然我现在还没能接受女上位
And since I'm not ready to try being on top yet,
我决定明天跟你去球馆看你打球
I'm gonna come watch you bowl tomorrow.
真的吗  好  那太好了
Really? Okay, great.
麦克斯  你想一起来吗
Hey, Max, you wanna come too?
我队伍里有一些帅哥呢
Got some cute guys on my bowling team.
应该说  有一些不是胖子的男人
Well, just some guys that aren't that fat.
毕竟也只是个保龄球队而已
It's a bowling team.
以喝啤酒为中心的消遣  还有有曲线的男人
Beer-based recreation? Men with curves?
我们是要去保龄球馆还是天堂啊
Are we going to a bowling alley or heaven?
麦克斯  我准备好去打保龄球啦
Max, I'm ready to go bowling.
你打扮得像准备好被
You look like you're ready for a greaser
50年代油头男带去山上"看夜景"
to feel you up at Make Out Point.
我等了那么久才盼到这个男朋友
I've waited long enough to have a boyfriend.
我可以为他喜欢上任何事物
I can learn to like anything.
毕竟又不是像打保龄球那么土的事
I mean, it's not like it's bowling.
天啊  还真是打保龄球
Oh, my God, it's bowling!
我就爱保龄球
Well, I loved it.
在打出满分300分后  我挂起护腰退休了
But I hung up my back brace after I bowled a 300.
我想在巅峰退休  就像罗伯·施奈德
I wanted to go out on top, like Rob Schneider.
而根据我听到的  你就不喜欢在上面[巅峰]
And from what I hear, apparently not you.
姑娘们
Hi, girls.
芭芭拉比我想象中还蠢
Yeah, Barbara's even dumber than I thought.
她跟隔壁的孩子有个玩耍约会
Yeah, she had a play date with the baby next door.
而人家都能识字了
And he can read.
吉米吗
Jimmy?
他都37岁了
He's 37.
他是个侏儒
He's a little person.
还是个税务律师
And a tax attorney.
我的确有觉得他一个孩子独居有点奇怪
Well, I did think it was odd that he lived alone.
我们要带芭芭拉去打保龄球
We're taking Barbara bowling.
有闪烁的霓虹灯还有打架闹事
Between the flashing lights and the fist fights,
没有任何地方比保龄球馆
nothing's more stimulating for a baby's brain
更能刺激宝宝大脑发育了
than a bowling alley.
比如读本书呢
How about a book?
跟保龄球有关的书吗
On bowling?
这就是保龄球馆啊
So, this is a bowling alley.
其实没那么糟嘛
This actually isn't so bad.
那是什么声音
What was that?
是人生已走到死路的人的声音
The sound of people going nowhere.
如果您是来参加短袜舞会  您晚来了40年
If you're here for the sock hop, it was 40 years ago.
我开玩笑的  你看起来美极了
I'm kidding, I'm kidding. You look sexy.
谢谢  我是来支持你的
Thank you. I'm here to support you
因为这是你的爱好
because this is what you love.
你爱什么  我就爱什么
And what you love, I love.
别再发出那声音了好吗
That seriously has to stop.
他是法兰克  他是我们球队的王牌
Hey, this is Frank. He's the star of our team.
自我介绍一下吧  弗兰克
Tell 'em about yourself, Frank.
我是我们球队的王牌
Well, I'm the star of our team.
我还喜欢吃晚餐
I also enjoy dinner.
棒呆了  又帅又傻
Yes! Cute and dumb.
在我过去的人生中  你都上哪去了
Where have you been all my life?
我念了十年高中
Well, I was in high school for ten years.
来吧  来打球
All right, let's bowl.
我们要往那声音方向去吗
We're going towards the sound?
这里的打炮亭居然还有帘子
A curtain on the sex booth?
高档地方啊  我们去投票的地方
Classy place. They had the same thing
也有这样的打炮亭
on the sex booth where we voted.
你是说试图投票的地方吧
You mean tried to vote.
我都还没怎么拉动开始投票的杠杆
I mean, I barely started pulling your lever
就被人踢出来了
before they kicked us out.
芭芭拉  芭芭拉  你感觉如何
Barbara, Barbara, what do you think?
感觉自己变聪明点了吗
You feel smarter yet?
你知道吗  要读懂这孩子
You know what? This baby's harder to read
比要读懂切尔西·汉德勒的回忆录还难
than Chelsea Handler's memoir.
快看  奥列格  她喜欢夹娃娃机
Oh, look, Oleg. She likes the claw machine.
她上一次对东西产生兴趣
This is the first thing she's been interested in
还是上次看到楼里那位女士从楼梯摔下去呢
since she saw that lady fall down the stairs in our building.
那真是太好笑了
That was hilarious.
她当时拿着一大碗砂锅菜
She was carrying a casserole bowl.
我要给她赢一个娃娃
You know, I am gonna win her a stuffed animal
告诉她我们虽然不是天才父母
and show her we may not be geniuses,
但我们他妈的可会操作迷你吊车了
but damn it, we can operate tiny cranes.
所以这颗小圆杆是什么玩意
Now what's this knobby thing do?
这是我们其他的队员  伯尼  利奈特
So this is the rest of our team. Bernie, Lynette,
然后是弗兰克  他正在试图
there's Frank again, who's currently trying
用没拆包装的吸管喝雪碧
to drink a Sprite through a wrapped straw.
他什么都不懂的样子太可爱了
So cute how he doesn't know stuff.
这些是球手娇妻  无意冒犯  韦恩
And these are the bowling wives. No offense, Wayne.
不介意  我就差一副合适的耳环
Oh, none taken. I'm a pair of sensible earrings
就是我妈的翻版了
away from being my mother.
今晚是在为明晚的比赛做练习
So this is the practice for the title game tomorrow night.
我们明晚打赢
We win that,
我们就能去底特律打冠军赛
we get to go to the championships in Detroit.
赢那个比赛  我们就能活着离开底特律
We win that, we get to leave Detroit.
太好了  我刚好可以找克哥讨没给的工钱
Oh, cool, I still have to pick up my last check from Chrysler.
他是帮我拉皮条的
He was my pimp.
球手娇妻们必需得跟去...
Uh, do the bowling wives have to go to that...
那些赢了还能再去哪哪的比赛吗
get to come to that?
可以啊  能来就太好了
Sure, that'd be great.
这可以是我们的专属爱好  你可以当我的球手娇妻
This could be our thing. You could be my bowling wife.
在我答应之前  我想问一下
Before I say yes, is there any way
这里的啤酒吧有卖白葡萄酒吗
the bar here serves white wine?
情侣都得这样为对方牺牲  对吧
Well, this is what couples do for each other, right?
我相信你的伴侣也会支持
I'm sure your spouses support you
你心中觉得重要的事物
in whatever's important to you.
伯尼错过我上周联邦法官的宣誓仪式
Bernie missed my swearing in as a Federal judge last week.
但他打了个180分  这波不亏
But he bowled a 180, so it was worth it.
今天是我生日  我抗癌成功一周年了
Today's my birthday. I'm one year cancer free.
利奈特压根就不知道我病过
Lynette didn't even know I was sick.
上啊  弗兰克  给老娘摇摆一下
Let's go, Frank. Shake it for mama!
他上的十年高中真是啥都没教会他
Those ten years in high school did nothing for him.
轮到我啦  好运两步舞
I'm up. Good luck two-step.
上啊  小鲍比  出手  没人比
Let's go, Bobby! Do a good jobby!
如果弗兰克没人比  那我也"出手"帮他
If Frank does a good jobby, I might just give him one.
鲍比鲍比比  最爱就是你
B-O-B-B-Y, I could be his alibi.
对手全是屁  全场最牛逼
'Cause he's bowling. He's bowling.
你能别加油了吗
You wanna cut that out?
我们就盼着他们输  如果他们赢了
We want them to lose. If they win tomorrow,
他们赛季就还得再多打两个月
the season goes on for two more months.
我们在这里不是已经过了两个月了吗
Haven't we already been here two months?
爽足止汗喷雾闻多了  会让你产生幻觉
The foot spray plays games with your mind.
麦克斯  你能过来闻闻我吗
Max, can you come sniff me?
虽然我希望我们浴室的下水道味
I was hoping the sewer smell from our shower
能掩盖保龄球馆的臭味
would cover the stink from the bowling alley,
但我想这两者已经融合在一起了
but I think they just joined forces.
如果你闻起来像下水道和保龄球馆的味道
If you keep smelling like sewers and bowling alleys,
那恐怕我们得滚床单了
we're gonna have to have sex.
你没这个福分了
Well, unfortunately for you,
我身上不会再有保龄球馆的味道
I won't be smelling like a bowling alley anymore
因为我要告诉鲍比
because I'm gonna tell Bobby that
保龄球应该是他的专利
bowling should be his thing.
在家美美地等他回来  则是我的专利
And waiting for him cutely at home will be mine.
说件有趣的事
Onto something interesting,
弗兰克昨晚来这里了
Frank came over last night.
你们俩上床了吗
You guys had sex?
我没有听见你的性爱小铃铛响啊
I didn't hear you ring your sex bell.
我们想来着  但他一脸懵逼
Well, we tried to, but he just seemed confused
所以我就让他先睡了
so I let him go to sleep.
但我有让他的双手好好干活
But I did put those hands to work.
我也没有听见你的手活蜂鸣器响啊
I didn't hear your hand stuff buzzer.
我让他帮我弄鞋带了
I had him work on my laces.
你没有听见我的鞋带卡祖笛响吗
You didn't hear my laces kazoo?
麦克斯
Hey, Max?
我把你鞋带上的结都解开了
I got all the knots out of your shoes.
如果我能教会他怎么做爱  怎么爬上床
If I can teach him how to have sex and how to climb onto a bed,
那这家伙我要定了
I'm locking this down.
想说给你送咖啡  给你个惊喜
Hey, thought I'd surprise you, bring you some coffee.
鲍比  你来这里干嘛
Bobby, what are you doing here?
这又不是保龄球馆
This isn't the bowling alley.
真高兴我找到他了  他妈一直在找他呢
Well, I'm glad I found him. His mom was looking for him.
来  弗兰克  走吧
Come on, Frank, let's go.
-我们得为比赛作准备了  -先走了
- We gotta get ready for the game. - Bye.
晚点球馆见
I'll see you later at the alley.
还是算了吧
No... okay.
我可以打给你吗
So, can I call you?
拜托告诉我那不是他打保龄球的手
Please tell me that wasn't his bowling hand.
卡洛琳  你对弗兰克做了什么
Caroline, what did you do to Frank?
他是我们的王牌球手
He's our best player.
这真的是意外
It was totally an accident.
我完全支持你的爱好  我一直很期待
I support your hobby. I was looking forward
今晚去看比赛  而不是在这里美美地等你回来
to coming tonight and not waiting here, cutely.
我没事
I'm fine.
我的小指本来就是最长那根手指吗
Is my pinky supposed to be my longest finger?
现在我们怎么办
What are we gonna do?
正如我对《致命捕捞》的制作人所说的那样
Well, like I told the producers of Deadliest Catch,
看来麦克斯船长要重出江湖了
looks like Captain Max is coming out of retirement.
还好我的保龄球手套还在
Good thing I still have my bowling glove.
麦克斯  那是微波炉手套
Max, that's an oven mitt.
老娘就是有这么厉害
That's how good I am.
不要有压力  但如果你搞砸了
No pressure, but if you blow this,
我可能这辈子都嫁不出去了
I may never get married.
拜托  我曾经靠打保龄球打出一条离开朝鲜的路
Oh, please, I once had to bowl to get out of North Korea.
麦克斯·布莱克  麦克斯·布莱克
Max Black, Max Black!
曾靠打球得自由  打到对手跪地求
She bowled to get her freedom back.
好量身定制的助威口号啊
That is a very specific cheer.
牛逼吧
Shabooya!
喜欢吗  废柴们
You like that, suckers?
保龄球不再是多次醉驾男人的天下啦
Bowling is not just for guys with their third DUI anymore.
麦克斯  那真是太厉害了
Max, that was amazing.
我是说刚才那一球  你现在的举动就有点怪了
The strike, I mean... what you're doing now is very off-putting.
或许这样有助于你理解  想象她在骑
Well, it makes more sense if you imagine she's riding
一只非常小的独角兽  名叫提托
a very small unicorn named Tito.
-好吧  看懂了  -对吧
- Oh, yeah, yeah. - Yeah.
瞧瞧这可怜的小家伙
Look at this poor sucker.
老子昨天在这台机子上浪费了400块的硬币
I wasted $400 in quarters yesterday on this thing.
祝你好运  孩子
Good luck, kid.
好吧  他夹到了
Oh. He won.
厄尔有像爪子一样的手
Well, between Earl's claw-like hand
而阿憨就出生于其中一台夹娃娃机
and the fact that Han was born in one of these machines,
我们组了个明星梦之队啊
we've got a dream team here.
这是我们的"一个半罗汉"
Now this is our Ocean's 1 1/2.
你答应过我  如果我帮芭芭拉夹到一个毛绒玩具
Now, you promised, if I win Barbara the stuffed animal,
你会来参加我的真人版妙探寻凶
you'll come to my live action Clue party.
我要扮演梅教授
I'll be playing Professor Plum.
将他重塑为善于发现问题的英国雅痞
Re-imagined as an English dandy with a nose for trouble.
好啊  那我就扮演不会出现的男管家
Great, and I'll play the butler who doesn't show up.
我是说  我们都不会去  对吧
I mean, we're not going, right?
对
No!
你们知道我能听见你们说话吧
You know I can hear you?
那你就知道我们都不会去啦
Well, then you know we're not going.
麦克斯  麦克斯  她真有种
Max, Max, she's got spunk!
略有醉意  依旧能中
And she's only slightly drunk.
我从来没试过喝五瓶啤酒就略有醉意
I haven't been slightly drunk in five beers.
我觉得我们赢定了
I think we got this.
多谢你残忍地把弗兰克搞残废了
Thanks for horribly maiming Frank.
再倒两个瓶子  我们就可以去底特律了
Two more pins and we're going to Detroit.
等待球[睾丸]落下中
Waiting for my ball to drop.
我的人生故事啊
Story of my life.
这家伙懂我在说什么
This guy knows what I'm talking about.
不  我不懂
No, I don't.
我帮你拿球吧  麦克斯
Lemme get the ball for you, Max.
在吃到饱印度自助餐馆时  我对你说过
Look, like I said to you at that all-you-can-eat Indian buffet,
除非你想被咬  否则别挡路
unless you wanna get bit, get out of the way.
在印度自助餐馆时  我也对你说过
And like I said to you at the Indian buffet,
我只想参与其中
I just want to be part of this.
妈的  我的手指
Damn it, my fingies!
麦克斯  对不起
Max, I'm sorry!
卡洛琳  瞧你干的好事
Caroline, what did you do?
你给我们队带来的伤害比
You're doing more damage to the team
我们在意式餐厅试图分开算账时还大
than when we tried to get separate checks at Macaroni Grill.
酒我没喝  为啥要我摊
Hey, if I don't drink, I don't pay.
这可是我掏咸菜罐的惯用手
Eh, this was my pickle-snatching hand.
就像我在印度自助餐馆说的那样
Like I said at the Indian buffet,
我觉得我们该叫救护车了
I think we might need an ambulance.
那真是我去过最疯狂的女厕所
Wow, that was the craziest woman's room ever.
里面全是小便池和男人
It was filled with urinals and men.
等等  好像走错了
Wait a minute.
你们给芭芭拉夹到毛绒玩具了吗
Hey, did you get the stuffed animal for Barbara yet?
还没  但更让人吃惊的事情发生了
No, but something more impressive happened.
我们至今没搞懂是怎么搞的
And we're still not sure how.
就像我看《先见之明》时说的那样
Like I said when I was watching the OA,
我他妈看的到底是什么啊
what the hell am I looking at?
从好的一面看  或许她没有你想得那么傻
On the bright side, maybe she's not as dumb as you thought.
那台夹娃娃机比我邻居艾琳
That claw machine is harder to get into
要难"进入"多了
than my neighbor Irene.
我们就两秒钟没看着她
We looked away for two seconds.
某个12岁的小屁孩刚在嘲笑阿憨
Some 12-year-olds were making fun of Han,
于是我们也加入了他的行列
so we piled on.
我们得赶紧把她弄出来
We gotta get her out of there.
好吧  我负责逗她开心
All right. I'll keep her entertained
你们操纵夹子从后面偷偷接近她
and you guys sneak up behind her with the claw.
麦克斯  你的手指应该没断吧
Max, so you don't think it's broken, do you?
我知道你一直很想要个手钩
I know you've always wanted a hook,
但我不想成为罪魁祸首
but I don't wanna be the cause of it.
有没有可能用你的左手继续比赛
Is there any way you can use your left?
不可能  这只手是摆设
Out of the question. This one's just for show.
在紧急情况下  别人可以代替麦克斯上场
In an emergency, someone else can bowl for Max,
但由于我们在比赛中
but since we're mid-game,
替她的人必须跟她同一性别
it must be someone of the same gender.
我本来想在跟你说这话之前  看看这事怎么解决
I was gonna see how this worked out before I dropped it on you.
因为我也是联盟的委员
I'm also league commissioner.
我敢说你们俩肯定有人会打保龄球
I'm sure one of you knows how to bowl.
不是有成见  但瞧瞧你俩
Not to stereotype, but look at you.
球手娇妻  球手娇妻
Bowling wives! Bowling wives!
是时候帮帮我们的球手去
It's time to help our bowling guys.
我们应该帮她吗  亲爱的
Think we should help her, hon?
没错  我们俩有私情
That's right, we're having an affair.
不要
And no.
好吧  他们俩不愿意
Yeah, they won't do it.
现在帮厄尔戴假发会不会太晚了
Is it too late to put Earl in a wig?
那得折腾好几个小时呢
Oh, that takes hours.
而我身上没带胶水
And I don't have the glue on me.
我们只能被迫放弃了
We're gonna have to forfeit.
我猜"不敢相信这居然不是落沟球"队
I guess I Can't Believe It's Not Gutter
要去底特律了
is going to Detroit.
而我真的不敢相信
And I can't believe it.
不  我可以打保龄球
No. I can do the bowling.
我必须行  因为我还得好几年才能接受女上位
I have to because I think I'm years away from being on top.
我有眩晕症
I have vertigo.
你太棒了
You are amazing.
你只需击倒两个木瓶
All you need is two pins.
就算你一个都不中
And even if you don't get them,
我依然爱你
I'll still love you.
但请务必击倒两个瓶子
But please get two pins.
卡洛琳  卡洛琳  她要靠自己
Caroline, Caroline, she's on her own.
如果没成功  孤独地死去
If she doesn't get this, she'll die alone.
麦克斯  你知道我有多讨厌这口号
Max, you know how much I hate that cheer.
我能去隔壁球场先练练怎么撂球吗
May I please have a practice swoop on the court next door?
其他人都有先练习啊
Everyone else got practice swoops.
她是不是觉得把球扔进球道里
Does she think rolling the ball down the lane
叫"撂球"
is called "swooping"?
我不知道  她还管床单叫"寝具"呢
I don't know. She calls sheets "bedding."
落沟球  有人要孤独地死去啦
Uh, gutter ball. Someone's dying alone.
那是我的错
Oh, that was my bad.
我应该告诉你  不要瞄准那两条球沟
I should have told you. Aim away from the gutters.
球沟就是两侧那玩意
The gutters are the things on the sides.
就...就专注中间
Just... just focus on the center,
手往后拉  然后...
whip it back, and...
或者这样也行
Or do that.
我的老天
Oh, my God!
十个瓶柱全倒了
The ten bases fell down!
我把它们都撂倒了
I swooped them all!
真是不可思议
That was incredible.
虽然我很不想说  但之前我有个疯狂的想法
I hate to say it, but I had this crazy thought
你是故意祸害我们球队
that you were trying to sabotage the team
因为你讨厌保龄球
because you hate bowling.
我也是这么想的
I thought so, too!
那下面有人
There's someone down there.
麦克斯
Max?
你们作弊
You cheated!
这不能怪[球瓶]我
You can't pin this on me.
芭芭拉是怎么钻进夹娃娃机的呢
How did Barbara get in the claw machine?
我们已经排除掉魔法
Well, we've ruled out magic.
现在我们最靠谱的想法是隐形的地精
Currently, our top theory is invisible gnomes.
是啊  她可能不是天才
Yeah, she may not be a genius,
但她勇于追求内心所需
but she goes after what she wants.
就像奥列格上乱交瑜伽时那样
Like Oleg at Swingers Yoga.
你真该看看苏菲钻进去抓她时
What you really had to see was Sophie going in after her.
她的脸朝下  塑身衣全露
She was face down, Spanx up.
天  那画面太疯狂了
Man, it was wild.
我们最好赶紧离开这  趁他们还没发现
All right, we better get going before they realize
我们弄坏了他们的夹娃娃机和打炮亭
we broke their claw machine and their sex booth
以及两台安全套贩卖机
and two of the condom machines.
还会有下一赛季
There's always next season.
到时候我们卷土重来  我可以想更多助威口号
We'll get back at it. I can work on some cheers.
你再也不许来这里了
You are never coming here again.
谢谢
Thank you!
开个球道亲好吗
Get a lane!
轻点  拉里
Take it easy, Larry.
那是我的手铐
Those are my handcuffs.
总有一天  我也能来保龄球馆打球
One day, I'll be able to come to a bowling alley
而不用这么被人押出去
without leaving like this.